Hey, brother.
أخي.
Look how close they are.
إنهما مقربان جداً.
Do you feel like
هل لديك شعور
a cuckold now?
على رأسك؟
Get lost.
اغرب عن وجهي
Okay.
حسنا
Circle Man.
البطل
I was so worried about you.
لا تعرف كم أقلق عليك
Knowing that you haven't come out of Elixir Village,
أعلم أنك لم تخرج في قرية الطب المقدس
I was so worried that I couldn't eat.
كنت قلقة حتى لا أستطيع تناول الطعام
I can't
نامي
sleep either.
لا أستطيع النوم
Don't worry.
لا تقلق
I'm fine.
أنا بخير
Circle Man.
محارب
Can I stay behind you
هل يمكنني أن أتبعك
and help you?
في المستقبل
Let me repay you.
دعني أرد لك الجميل
Goodness.
يا إلهي
Miss.
آنستي
Miss, please get up.
انهضي يا آنسة
We just met by chance.
لقد التقينا بالصدفة
We are all people of the martial arts world.
أبناء عالم الكونغ فو
Don't be like this.
لا داعي لهذا
I'm not just trying to repay you.
في الواقع أنا لا أفعل ذلك فقط لأرد الجميل
I really admire your style.
أنا معجب بك
You're the most courageous hero I've ever met.
أنت الفارس الأكثر شجاعة في حياتي
He...
إنه
He what?
ماذا؟
Don't be afraid.
لا تخف لا تخف
I'm here.
أنا هنا
The sun today
الشمس اليوم
is so dazzling.
‫مدهش جدا‬
Who was that?
من كان ذلك؟
Why does he seem a little abnormal?
لماذا أشعر أنه غير طبيعي
Yes.
نعم نعم
He
إنه
has some problems here.
هناك بعض المشاكل هنا
Let's continue our talk.
نحن نتحدث
We...
نحن
Circle Man.
محارب
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
I'm still unmarried.
أنا فتاة لم أتزوج
We can't do this.
لا يمكننا فعل هذا
No, no.
لا لا
Gosh.
يا إلهي
Do you understand?
هل فهمت؟
I don't want to lie to you.
لا أريد أن أكذب عليك
Actually, I'm just like you.
في الواقع أنا مثلك
I'm also a woman.
أنا أيضا فتاة
I disguised myself as a man
أنا أتظاهر بأنني رجل
to inquire for information.
من أجل الخروج للاستفسار
I don't believe you.
لا أصدق ذلك
You are
أنت
so cool
أنت وسيم جدا
and manly.
إنه رجل
I've never seen
لم يسبق لي أن رأيت
such a rough man like you.
الرجل الذي يحمي بقوة مثلك
No.
لا لا لا
Do you believe me now?
هل تصدقين؟
Sister, where do you live?
أختي، أين منزلك؟
Let me send you home.
ما رأيك أن أوصلها لك
You're alone outside.
أنت فتاة بالخارج
I'm worried.
لا أطمئن
I'm not going back.
لن أعود
I escaped from home.
لقد هربت
I can't go back now.
لا يمكنني العودة الآن
If I go back now,
إذا عدت الآن
I'll be married to a man I don't know.
سأتزوج من رجل لا يعرفني
He will also scold his wife.
حتى لا تعرفها
Have you discussed it with your family?
هل تناقشت مع عائلتك
It's useless.
لا فائدة
My brother always announces the result.
أخي دائماً يعلن النتائج
Normally, he just came to inform me.
عادةً ما يأتي لإبلاغي
He won't discuss with me.
لن يتناقش معي
He always said,
هو دائما يقول
what do you know?
ماذا تفهم؟
I chose the best ones for you.
أختار لك أفضل شيء
I know this too well.
أنا أفهم هذا
He thinks he cares about you.
هذا النوع الذي يعتقد أنه يفضل لك
But that's not what you think.
لكن في الواقع لا تفكرين هكذا على الإطلاق
Right?
أليس كذلك
Yes.
‫أليس كذلك؟‬
Actually,
في الواقع
what's the use of saying nice things?
ما فائدة كلامك
Who knows what will happen in the future?
لا أعرف ما سيحدث في المستقبل
Yes.
نعم
Sometimes,
أحيانا
don't look at
لا تنظر إلى هذا الشخص
how nice he said things
ما مدى اللطيفة التي يقولها
and how romantic his promise is.
وعد رومانسي
We have to look at
يعتمد على هذا الشخص
how he treats you
في اللحظة الحاسمة
I'm responsible for your safety.
يجب أن أكون مسؤولا عن سلامتك
Can I take a look at this cabinet?
هل يمكنني إلقاء نظرة على هذا الخزانة؟
you stay.
ابق هنا
You're willing to keep me, Circle Man?
أنت على استعداد للبقاء معي أيها المحارب
We girls should help girls.
يجب أن نساعد الفتيات
You can stay here
أنت هنا
as long as you want.
يمكنك البقاء كما تشاء
I'm here.
أنا هنا
I'll protect you.
سأحميك
She's so cool.
‫إنها رائعة‬
No wonder she's my idol.
‫تستحق أن تكون مثلي الأعلى‬
Circle Man.
البطل
How about this?
هكذا
You have a good rest.
استريحي جيدا
Call me if you need anything.
اتصل بي إذا احتجت أي شيء
I'll be at the door.
أنا عند الباب
Come here.
تعال
What?
ماذا؟
Well.
ذلك
He's a man.
إنه رجل
How can he stay in your room?
كيف يمكنه أن يعيش في غرفتك؟
Let him sleep with me.
لماذا لا تدعه ينام معي؟
It's none of your business.
هذا ليس من شأنك
You're my ally now.
أنت تحالف معي الآن
Of course I should be responsible for your safety.
بالطبع يجب أن أكون مسؤولا عن سلامتك
I know this young hero very well.
أنا على دراية بهذا الفارس
He took action to uphold justice before.
لقد كنت رجلًا مخلصًا من قبل
So I'm quite safe.
لذلك أنا آمن
You met him not long after you came out.
لقد عرفته منذ متى خرجت
Let me tell you.
أقول لك
People in the martial arts world
الناس الذين يسافرون في عالم الكونغ فو
know how to read people by their looks.
سننظر إلى المظهر
I've observed him carefully.
لقد لاحظت هذا الشخص بعناية
His eyes are wretched.
عيناه شائبة
He's in a weird shape.
شكله غريب
He's also easy in his morals.
‫سلوك موج‬
He must be a bad guy.
لا بد أنه شيء جيد
How can you say he looks wretched
‫لقد قلت فقط لأن لديه خنجر‬
just because he has a beard?
‫أنت تقول أنها قبيحة‬
You're so mean.
كلامك قاسي جدا
Are you...
هل أنت
Are you jealous?
هل ستشعر بالغيرة؟
Impossible.
مستحيل
Xingchen.
النجوم
I really don't understand.
أنا حقاً لا أفهم
If you don't even like
إذا لم تعجبك
a man like me,
لا تحبه
what kind of man do you like?
أي نوع من الرجال تحبينه؟
Mu.
مو
I told you,
لقد أخبرتك
you have to
يجب أن تكون مثلي
be like me.
مثل أنا
I don't want a romantic relationship now.
لا أريد الحب بين الرجال والنساء الآن
I just want to focus on my career.
أريد فقط أن أعمل بجد
Xingchen,
شينج شين
no matter what you want to do,
مهما كنتِ تريدين أن تفعلي
I'm willing to do it with you.
أنا على استعداد لمرافقتك
If you want to explore the martial arts world,
إذا كنت تريد التجول في عالم الكونغ فو
I'll go with you.
سأرافقك
As long as I'm by your side,
طالما أنا بجانبك
you won't get hurt.
لن تتعرض لأي أذى
This is the promise
هذا هو
I made to you.
من الأخ مو
We have news, Brother.
هناك أخبار يا أخي
Tell me.
قل بسرعة
A family has just moved in
تحت دونج شان قرية تشي تشو
at the bottom of the east hill in Xicao Village.
في دونج شان
It's said that the surname of the man of the house is Chen.
قال أن المالك لقبه تشين
He got some strange disease and stayed at home.
أصيب بمرض غريب ولم يخرج
His wife always goes out to buy things.
كل مرة تخرج زوجته لشرائها
Everyone calls her Lady Yu.
الجميع يدعوها السيدة يو
I remember you said that
أتذكر أنك قلت
a hero was bitten by a mutant
في زنزانة قرية الطب المقدس
in the dungeon of Elixir Village.
هناك محارب تم عضه من قبل الغرباء
Chen Jie.
‫تشيان تشيان‬
has a childhood sweetheart.
لديه خطيبة كبرت
Yu?
شياو يو
They are not on the list of mutants
في قائمة أسماء الغرباء
in the list of Elixir Village.
بدونهم
They must have escaped.
لا بد أنهم هربوا
Where did Chen Jie and Yu go?
أين ذهب تشن هو وشياو وانغ؟
We went through so much trouble to get here, but they're not here.
لم يكن من السهل أن يأتي إلى هنا
Have you found Chen Jie?
هل يوجد مساعد تشين
They've got help.
هناك شخص يساعدهم
They're out of danger now.
لقد هربوا من الخطر
But I don't know where they went.
لا أعرف أين ذهب
Maybe
ربما
the clue is still there.
‫هذا الدليل لم ينقطع
Have you found anything? Brother.
هل وجدت ذلك يا أخي
Think about it.
فكر في الأمر
Xingchen
النجوم
was back to normal after taking the medicine.
لقد تعافيت بعد تناول الدواء
Chen Jie didn't take any medicine.
لم يتناول الدواء
How did he stay clearheaded?
كيف ظل مستيقظاً؟
Are these people related to men in black again?
هل هم على اتصال بهؤلاء الملابس السوداء؟
But no one has been here since yesterday.
لكن لم يأت أحد من الأمس حتى الآن
What a coincidence. We meet again.
يا لها من صدفة، نلتقي مرة أخرى
I was worried about Xingchen.
لأنني قلقة على النجوم
I was worried too, so I followed.
لذلك جئت إلى هنا
Did I cause you trouble?
هل أزعجكم؟
just arrived?
وصلت للتو
Yes.
نعم نعم
I have a question.
لدي سؤال
did you know we are here?
كيف عرفت أننا هنا
I asked people on my way.
لذا سألتنا طوال الطريق
Xingxing.
النجوم
and see if there are any other clues.
لنذهب ونرى إذا كان هناك أي أدلة أخرى
Sir,
أيها المحارب
you don't have to go.
لا داعي أن تذهب
We don't need that many people.
لا تحتاج إلى الكثير من الناس
It's okay.
لا بأس
Have a good rest.
استريحي جيدا
Who are you?
من أنت؟
Why did you tie us up?
لماذا تربطنا
Yin Fengmian,
يا صاحب وادي ين لينغ
Young Master of Yinling Valley.
لجذب فينج ميان
Sir,
أيها المحارب
please.
أرجوك
Please let us go.
أرجوك اتركني أنا وأبي
Since you are conscious,
بما أنك واع
you can understand me, right?
يمكنك أن تفهم ما أقوله، أليس كذلك؟
Why can you stay clear-minded?
لماذا يمكنك البقاء مستيقظاً؟
We really don't know.
نحن حقا لا نعرف
The point
المفتاح
should still be Huo Xingchen.
يجب أن يكون على جسد "هيو شينغ تشين"
Why are you still up?
لماذا لم تنم بعد؟
Is something bothering you?
هل هناك شيء في قلبك؟
Let me ask you a question.
أسألك سؤالا
What kind of person
هل تعتقد
do you think
أيها الرجل
the Big Beard is?
كيف حاله؟
Brother,
أخي الكبير
I think he's nice
أعتقد أنه شخص جيد
and loyal.
إنه مخلص
One time at the inn,
ذات مرة في الفندق
he understood the new move I created.
أدرك مهارتي الخاصة
He even shouted.
لقد أصرخ
What did he shout?
ماذا صرخ؟
Pull
‫بقوة‬
and the river.
نهر شي
My move
حيلتي تلك
used Xiang Yu's momentum not to cross the river.
‫استخدمت قوة شيانغ يو لا يمر النهر‬
It's tragic and majestic.
.إنه مثير للشفقة والشجاع
Is this what I was asking you?
هل قلت لك هذا؟
What?
ماذا تريد أن تقول؟
I mean this person.
أعني هذا الشخص
Don't you think
ألا تعتقد أنه
he is a little weird?
أنه غريب؟
Weird?
غريب
I see.
فهمت
Do you think Miss Huo's eyes
هل تعتقد أن عينيها
are staring at his beard every day?
تراقب لحيته كل يوم
Don't worry.
لا تقلق
No one can steal my brother's woman.
لا يمكن لأحد سرقة امرأة أخي الأكبر
When you practice swordsmanship,
ألا يمكنك
can you also train your mind?
هل يمكنك أن تغذي عقلك؟
I was talking about
أقصد هذا الشخص
how he often appears out of nowhere.
غالبًا ما يظهر بدون سبب
Didn't you notice?
ألم يكتشف ذلك؟
Keep an eye on him.
راقبه
It's not because of Huo Xingchen.
ليس بسبب "هيو شينغ تشين"
You're still so stubborn.
ما زلت عنيدًا
You just think
ألا تعتقد
they are too close.
أنهما قريبان جدا
Okay.
حسنا
I knew it.
كما توقعت
Huo Xingchen and the others are still here.
ما زال "هيو شينغ تشين" هنا
Jiang Buying,
جيانغ بو فاز في المرتبة الثالثة في عالم الكونغ فو
was caught?
هل تم اكتشافه؟
Why are you practicing at night?
ما هذا السيف الذي تدربته في منتصف الليل؟
Since I can't attack by force.
لا يمكنك الهجوم بقوة
I'll use my wisdom.
إذا سأستخدم ذكائي
Run! Run!
اركض بسرعة
Many mutants came from the woods behind the village.
هناك الكثير من الغرباء خلف القرية
So scary.
هذا مخيف
Hurry up! Run!
اركض بسرعة
Xingxing, wait.
النجوم، انتظر
I don't think it's that simple.
أعتقد أن الأمر ليس بهذه البساطة
Don't you think
ألا تعتقدون
the news came at the right time?
أن هذا الخبر جاء في الوقت المناسب
How about this?
هكذا
Xingxing and I
أنا والنجوم
go to the woods for a check first.
سنذهب إلى الغابة الصغيرة هناك للتحقق
Buying,
الفوز خطوة بخطوة أنت
you stay here with him.
هذا الأخ الكبير
You stay here.
ابقوا هنا
If men in black come, you can deal with them.
سيكون من السهل التعامل مع شخص يرتدي ملابس أسود
Can we change groups?
هل يمكنك تغيير المجموعة؟
I'll team up with Xingchen.
أنا مع النجوم في الفريق
Is it better for people who know each other well to team up?
هل من الأفضل أن تشكل الأعباء؟
I think you're right.
أعتقد أن الأخ الأكبر على حق
What are you talking about?
ما الصحيح
I grouped like that for a reason.
هذا منطقي
You have to keep an eye on Big Beard.
يجب أن تراقب لحية كبيرة
If anything is unusual about him,
إذا كان هناك شيء غير طبيعي
please tell me later.
أخبرني بعد ذلك
Xingchen and I
أنا و النجوم
used to work together.
كنا نعمل معاً
We have a tacit understanding.
في العمل معًا
Can you understand that?
هل تفهمين
Fine.
حسنا
Something is wrong with the fog.
هذا الضباب غريب
Someone must have
يجب أن يكون هناك شخص
lure us into the woods on purpose.
يريد أن يقودنا إلى الغابة
Could it be the mastermind?
هل تعتقد أنه القاتل وراء ذلك؟
It's possible.
هذا ممكن
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
I'm afraid there might be a trap.
أخشى أن يكون هناك فخ
We should hold hands to prevent accidents.
أمسك بيدك لمنع الحوادث
What accident can there be?
ماذا يمكن أن يحدث
Listen.
دعني أخبرك
You agreed me to keep the promise.
لقد وعدتني بوعدي
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل
Since we can't hold hands, I'll just hold a branch.
إذا لم تستطيعي الإمساك بيديك
Huo Xingchen!
"هيو شينغ تشين"
Xingxing, stop it. Come out.
النجوم، توقف، اخرج
Who are you?
من أنت؟
Why did you tie me up?
لماذا ربطتني؟
What about the person who was with me?
كيف هو الشخص الذي كان معي؟
You two really love each other.
أنتما حقا تحب الفراشة
Your life is at stake.
لا تستطيعون الحفاظ على حياتكم
But you're still thinking about your lover?
ما زلت تفكر في عشيقك
Here.
تعال
What did you do to him?
ماذا فعلت به؟
You were bitten by a mutant.
لقد عضه الغرباء
How did you go back to normal?
لماذا عدت إلى طبيعتك؟
Huo Xingchen!
"هيو شينغ تشين"
Since you don't have the antidote,
بما أنك لا تملك الترياق
then die with Ci.
فلتموت مع شياو سي
Xingxing.
النجوم
Buting, are you all right?
بودينغ هل أنت بخير
Let her go!
أطلق سراحه بسرعة
Why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
Don't you dislike me?
ألم تكرهني؟
Leave now.
اذهب بسرعة
Who said I dislike you?
من قال إنني أكرهك
If I dislike you, why would I be willing to be buried with you in water
إذا كنت تكرهك سأدفنك في الماء
twice?
مرتين
Are you stupid? Leave!
‫أنت غبي اذهب بسرعة‬
Leave!
اذهب بسرعة
Why should I leave?
لماذا يجب أن أذهب؟
I was wondering who it was.
كنت أعتقد من
It's so dazzling.
‫هذا مثير للغاية‬
Today,
اليوم
no matter what,
على أي حال
I will kill you.
سأقتلك
Who do you want to kill?
من تريد أن تقتلني؟
If you want to kill me, why didn't you put me in?
‫إذا قتلتني لن تسمح لي بالدخول‬
Are you stupid?
هل أنت غبي؟
Open the door.
افتح الباب
Why do you want the door open?
‫لا تفتح الباب
You want to come in?
هل تريد الدخول؟
Fine.
حسنا
I'd like to see
أريد أن أرى
how you lovers
كيف مات
die in front of me?
كيف مات أمامي
Come on, open it.
تعال افتح
Blah, blah...
توقف عن الكلام
What are you yelling about?
لماذا تصرخ
Stop fighting.
ماذا؟
Who's a couple with him?
من؟ من هو حبيبه؟
Who said that?
من قال ذلك
He's always following me.
‫يلاحقني كل يوم
I hate him.
أكرهه كثيرا
I...
أنا
I don't like him at all.
لا أحبه على الإطلاق
What couple?
أي علاقة؟
Jiang Buting, let me tell you.
جيانغ بو تينغ دعني أخبرك
Let's agree on a three-point law.
ثلاثة قواعد
First, stay away from me.
أولاً ابتعد عني
Second,
ثانيا
we're in the martial arts world.
نحن نتجول في عالم الكونغ فو
We shouldn't talk about love.
في عالم الكونغ فو
Third, let me tell you.
ثالثاً سأخبرك
A melon twisted off its stem before it's ripe doesn't taste sweet. (Forced love does not last.)
البطيخ القوي ليس حلوًا
I don't like melons.
أنا لا أحب القرع
Why would I twist one off?
لماذا يجب أن أزيل البطيخ
Yeah.
نعم
Cut the crap.
توقف عن الهراء
Go to hell!
موتوا جميعاً
Don't come over.
لا تقتربوا
Be careful.
احذر
No.
لا
Xingxing, be careful.
انتبه النجوم
Ci.
شياو سي
Take care of yourself, Xingxing.
اعتني بنفسك أولا النجوم
Xingxing, are you hurt?
النجوم، هل تأذيت؟
I told you to leave. Why didn't you leave?
طلبت منك أن تغادر، لماذا لم تغادر؟
Are you worried about me?
أنت قلق علي
Who's worried about you?
من يقلق عليك
I was worried about the twisted melon.
أنا قلق بشأن ذلك البطيخ القوي
I wouldn't know if the melon is sweet
هل البطيخ القوي حلو أم لا
until I twist it off.
أنا "هيو شينغ تشين" لم أكن أعلم
Are you two done?
هل انتهيتما؟
Jianwa.
أخ جيان وا
Binghe.
أخي بينغ خه
I've been waiting for you here for a long time.
لقد انتظرتك هنا لفترة طويلة
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
Your sister disappeared
عندما ذهبت إلى قرية تشي تشو
on the day you went to Xicao Village.
اختفت أختك
But my men found out that
لكن وجدت رجالي
your sister also went to Xicao Village.
ذهبت أختك إلى قرية تشي تشو أيضا
Binghe.
نهر الجليد
Mutants are not incurable.
‫ليس الغرباء لا يوجد علاج‬
You shouldn't have killed them.
لا يجب أن تقتلهم
Uncle!
عمي
Jianwa.
جيان وا
Emergency report from Yinling Valley.
أخبار عاجلة من وادي ين لينج
It's from the Young Master of Yinling Valley.
جاء من صاحب وادي ين لينج
Yinling Valley is under control.
تم السيطرة على وادي ين لينج
He requested the Wuyue Sect to eliminate villains.
أطلب من طائفة وو يوه
This is outrageous.
هذا غير معقول
Pass my order down.
أصدر الأوامر
Gather our men
اجمع الجنود على الفور
to Yinling Valley.
إلى وادي ين لينج
This is the first batch of elixir
هذا هو الدواء الساحر
made with the new furnace by the master hand.
أول دواء سحري مصنوع من المبخرة الجديدة
It is more effective than before.
أفضل من قبل
Thank you for the medicine.
شكراً لك على إعطائي الدواء
I'll work with utter devotion
يجب أن يكون وادي ين لينج خبيراً
for you.
حتى الموت
Circle Man and Jiang Buting
المحارب والجيانغ بو دينغ
have been out for so long
لقد خرجت منذ وقت طويل
and hasn't come back yet.
ولم يعد بعد
Are they in danger?
هل سيكون هناك خطر
Should I go out and look for them?
هل يجب أن أذهب للبحث عنهم؟
No, I have to find him.
لا يجب أن أذهب للبحث عنه
Trying to escape?
هل تريد الهروب؟
He's sneaking around.
هذا الأخ الكبير يختبئ
No, I have to keep an eye on him.
لا يجب أن أراقبه
I didn't know
لم أتوقع ذلك
he's a Kungfu maniac just like me.
هذا الأخ الأكبر هو مجنون في الفنون القتالية مثلي
I heard that there are heroes who bind their limbs
سمعت أن هناك محارب يربط يديه وقدميه
to increase their power invisibly.
ويزيد القوة بلا شكل
Is he training himself
هل يمكن أن يكون الأخ الأكبر هكذا
like that day and night?
تدرب نفسك ليلا ونهارا
I really admire him.
هذا مثير للإعجاب حقًا
Come on.
هيا
Buying.
الأخ بو شينغ
If you're really worried,
إذا كنت قلقًا حقًا
we can go and have a look.
سنذهب ونرى
Seeing you walking around
أراك تجول هنا
makes my eyes blurry.
أنت مشوشة
Don't play tricks.
لا تلعب الحيل
Although I think you are a nice person,
على الرغم من أنك شخص جيد
my brother asked me to take precautions against you.
لكن أخي طلب مني أن أحذرك
I have to listen to him.
لا يمكنني ألا أحرس
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Look.
انظر
I can't beat you.
لا يمكنني هزيمتك
I can't outrun you either.
لا يمكنني الهروب منك
We're tied together.
دعنا نربط معا
Even if I'm a bad guy,
حتى لو كنت شخص سيء
I can't run away.
لا يمكنني الهروب
Brother.
أخي الكبير
I didn't expect
لم أتوقع
I feel ashamed by your side.
أشعر بالخجل من بقائي معك
You're upright. I shouldn't have suspected you.
أنت صريح وواضح لا يجب أن أشك بك
We don't have to tie our hands together.
لا داعي أن نمسك بيدنا
If you're worried,
إذا كنت غير مطمئن
we can hold hands.
يمكننا أن نمسك بأيدي بعضنا البعض
Why?
لماذا نمسك بيدنا
Just tie them together.
ربطها
Two men...
رجلان
Done, Brother.
حسناً يا أخي
Shameless!
يا لك من وقح
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
How did your brother become a mutant?
كيف أصبح أخوك شخص غريب؟
Fengci and I were adopted by Yinling Valley since childhood.
لقد تبنى أنا و فينج سي من وادي ين لينج منذ صغرنا
We uphold the principle that the strong should be the head.
نحن في وادي ين لينج نقوم بإرسال القوة
But people of Yinling Valley
لكن الناس في وادي يين لينج
are extremely dumb in martial arts.
موهبة الفنون القتالية سيئة للغاية
In order to protect ourselves,
من أجل الدفاع عن النفس
Many people in the martial arts world disdain it.
الكثير من الناس في عالم الكونغ فو يحتقرون
I've heard about it.
سمعت عنه
But recently,
لكن في هذه الفترة
many people in our valley
كثير من الناس في وادي
have greatly improved their martial arts.
يزداد قوتهم بشكل غير متوقع
My position in the valley is also in danger.
وأنا في الوادي
Hou Qiong, come forward.
تعال إلى الأمام
This is the elixir given by the Master.
هذا دواء سحري من صاحب الوادي
Thank you for the medicine.
شكراً لك يا صاحب الوادي
Fifth Senior Brother, take it now.
أخي وو كلي بسرعة
It's such a good thing.
هذا الشيء الجيد
Don't let others have it.
لا يمكن أن تترك الآخرين
Yeah, take it now.
أجل، تناولي الطعام
Congratulations, Fifth Senior Brother.
تهانينا، وانج وو
Fifth Senior Brother, don't mind it.
وو، لا تهتم بهذا
I have one too.
وأنا أيضاً
What is this?
ما هذا؟
It's a symbol of glory.
هذا رمز شرف
We all have the elixir
لدينا
given by the Master.
دواء سحري من صاحب الوادي
It is so magical.
هذا رائع
It's just a tiny vein.
إنها مجرد قطعة صغيرة
Don't mention it.
لا تذكر ذلك
Yes.
نعم
Junior Feng was the first one to be given the medicine by the Master.
أول من أعطاه صاحب الوادي الدواء
He has the most prominent vein.
وأكثر آثاره
This is also the symbol of trust of the Master.
هذا رمز يثق به صاحب الوادي
I hid a so-called holy medicine.
أخفيت دواء مقدس
Untie me.
فك القيود لي
I'll get it for you.
سأحضره لكم
Do you need me to get it for you?
هل تحتاجين أن تعطيني إياه؟
Don't smell it.
لا تشمها.
But according to what you said,
لكن حسب ما قلته
after taking the medicine,
بعد تناول هذه الأدوية
they will become more powerful.
سوف يزداد قوتهم
There will also be veins on their bodies.
سيظهر خطًا على جسدهم
Isn't that the condition of mutants?
أليست هذه حالة غريبة؟
How many people in Yinling Valley
في وادي يين لينج
have taken this medicine?
كم من الناس تناولوا هذا الدواء؟
A lot.
كثير
Almost all of them.
‫تقريباً الجميع‬
But I didn't take it.
لكنني لم آكل
It's right that you didn't take it.
هذا صحيح
This black pill should be the same as the poisonous powder
هذه الحبة السوداء
that controlled mutants in the Elixir Village.
مسحوق السم الذي يتحكم فيه الغرباء
If they are really the same thing,
إذا كان هذا حقا شيء
then Yinling Valley
فإن وادي ين لينج
is the mastermind.
هو القاتل وراء الكواليس
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
Why is there no one here?
لماذا لا يوجد أحد هنا؟
Didn't the villagers say
ألم يقولوا القرويين للتو
there were mutants nearby?
أن هناك شخص غريب هنا
Xingchen.
النجوم
Xingchen, where are you?
أين أنت؟
Xingchen! Brother! Brother!
شينج شين
Don't panic.
لا داعي للذعر
Xingchen.
النجوم
Look.
انظر
Tracking Butterfly.
فراشة البحث
That's right.
صحيح
My brother really has an incredible foresight.
أخي توقع كل شيء
He said if we can't contact each other,
قال إذا لم نتمكن من التواصل مع بعضنا البعض
Tracing Butterfly can help us.
الفراشة التي يمكن أن تساعدنا
We're here.
وصلنا
This is
هذا هو
his incredible foresight?
توقعت الأشياء كالإله
It's just a small accident.
حادث صغير
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل
You don't understand.
أنت لا تفهم
Circle Man said
قال المحارب
we have to be bold and careful
يجب أن تكون شجاعًا وحذرًا
and make marks.
يجب أن نضع علامة
Who is Circle Man?
من هو الفارس؟
What Man?
ما هذا البطل
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
It's you.
إنه أنتم
Don't be afraid.
لا تخف
I'm not on their side.
أنا لست شريكهم
Are you Yu?
هل أنت شياو يو؟
I was with Chen Jie at the Elixir Village.
لقد كنت مع تشين تشيان في قرية الطب المقدس
He always talked about you.
لقد ذكرك دائماً
We're here to find someone.
نحن هنا للبحث عن شخص
If we can find him,
إذا وجدنا ذلك الشخص
Chen Jie might be saved.
ربما سينقذ تشين دونغ
Really?
حقاً؟
Have you found him?
هل وجدتم
We followed mutants' clues.
لقد جئنا مع أدلة غريبة
A senior doctor from Qingfeng Village told us
قال لنا طبيب كبير في قرية تشينج فينج
there is a mutant here.
أن هناك شخص غريب هنا
I didn't expect the mutant to be Chen Jie.
لم أتوقع أن الغريب هو كارثة قديمة
Is the senior doctor
أيها الطبيب الكبير
with gray hair
إنه أبيض
and looks thin and amiable?
‫يبدو نحيفًا ودقيقًا‬
I know...
أعرف
I know the doctor you mentioned.
أعرف الطبيب الذي ذكرته
You know him?
هل تعرفه؟
He's s doctor from Yinling Valley.
إنه طبيب في وادي ين لينج
Are you going to Yinling Valley？
هل ستذهبون إلى وادي ين لينج؟
Please take me with you.
يجب أن تأخذوني معك
I'm the Young Master of Yinling Valley.
أنا صاحب الوادي الصغير في وادي ين لينغ
No one is more suitable to lead the way than me.
لا أحد يناسب قيادة الطريق أكثر مني
They did this to my brother.
لقد آذوا أخي إلى هذا الحد
You have to believe me.
يجب أن تثقوا بي
There are traps and formations everywhere in Yinling Valley.
في وادي يين لينج مليء بالتشكيل
If no one leads the way,
إذا لم يرشدكم أحد
you can't even find the entrance.
لن تجدوا مدخل
Yu,
شياو يو
take Chen Jie to a safe place.
خذ تشين تشيان إلى مكان آمن
We'll go find the doctor.
لنذهب للبحث عن الطبيب
When we find the medicine,
عندما نجد الدواء
Chen Jie should be fine.
سوف يتعافى الكارثة القديمة
Be careful.
انتبهوا لسلامتكم
Don't worry.
لا تقلق
Let's go, Jie.
هيا يا هينج
Don't tie my legs.
‫اربط الناس لا تربط رجلك‬
You've gone too far!
لقد تجاوزتم حدودكم
Shut up!
اصمت
I'll tie your mouth up if you keep talking.
‫اربط فمك
Young Master.
سيدي
We got news from Hucang Guards.
هناك أخبار من الحرس الإمبراطوري
It's done.
تم التعامل معها
Uncle Huo.
العم هوه
There is news from the Hucang Guards who went to Xicao Village?
هناك أخبار من الحراس في قرية تشي تشو
Yin Fengmian.
لجذب فينج ميان
Are you sure you showed us the right way?
هل أنت متأكد أنك لم تأخذ الطريق الخطأ؟
This is the entrance to the back mountain of Yinling Valley.
هذا مدخل جبل خلف وادي ين لينج
You tied me up like this.
لقد ربطتني هكذا
I can't unlock the formation.
لا يمكنني فك العين
Hey!
أريدك أن تفكك القيود
not to change the way of tying.
لم أطلب منك تغيير طريقة ربطها
Done.
حسنا
You're so skilled.
أنت ماهر جدا
I used to help an old man tie pigs.
لقد تدربت على ربط الخنزير من أجل رجل عجوز
Let me tell you.
دعني أخبرك
You did harm to Xingchen before.
لقد قتلت النجوم
I won't set you free.
لن أدعك حرة
Go unlock the formation.
انزع التشكيلة
Divide the north and south.
إلى الشمال الجنوبي
Fix the heaven and earth.
يجب أن نكون
The push trigram on the left.
[المقدر الأيسر]
The elbow strike trigram on the right.
المقدر الأيمن
The heaven and earth is fixed.
لقد تم تحديد قوان كون
Let's go.
هيا بنا
Follow my steps.
اتبعني
You can't make a single misstep.
لا يمكنك أن تخطئ خطوة واحدة
Remember.
تذكر
Not a single misstep.
‫لا يمكن خطوة
Got it. Shut up.
عرفت
Master.
يا صاحب الوادي
Young Master sneaked in with evil-doers.
تسلل ابن الوادي مع شخص شرير
Fifth Senior Brother has taken people to arrest them.
قد أخذ وو رجاله للقبض عليه
A traitor is not qualified to be Young Master.
الخائن ليس مؤهلاً لتكون صاحب الوادي
Pass my order down.
أصدر الأوامر
Make sure to eliminate all of them.
يجب القضاء عليهم جميعا
We're at a critical moment.
هذه هي اللحظة الحاسمة
Anyone who ruins my plan
إذا أفسد أحد عملي
will be killed.
اقتلوهم جميعا
Master.
يا صاحب الوادي
Useless trash
عديم الفائدة
can only be my fertilizer
فقط يمكنني صنع أسمدة لي
and help me achieve great success.
لمساعدتي على النجاح
Master hand,
يا خبير
the new furnace has been activated for days.
تم نقل هذا المبخر الطبي منذ أيام
It has absorbed many people's power.
استنشقت الكثير من الناس
When will the elixir be made?
متى سينجح هذا الدواء السحري؟
His Highness is waiting for your elixir.
صاحب الجلالة ينتظر دوائك السحري
Calm down.
اهدأ
Those who achieve great things
يجب أن تكون هادئاً
You're right.
أنت على حق
Why are there so many men in black?
لماذا يوجد الكثير من الرجال الملابس السوداء؟
Did we poke into the lair of men in black?
هل طعنا عش الرجل ذو الزي الأسود؟
Maybe you are right.
ربما أنت محق
This place is nothing
مقارنة بتجارة الطب المقدس
compared with Elixir Village.
إنه مجرد ساحر
Useless!
عديم الفائدة
Keep searching.
استمر في البحث
Yes.
حاضر حاضر
Why are you so afraid of him?
لماذا أنت خائف منه؟
If he kills me,
إذا قتلني
he'll be the Young Master.
سيحصل على منصب صاحب الوادي
How can I not run?
لن أركض
The competition of Yinling Valley
أنت في وادي يين لينج
is so fierce.
منافسة شرسة للغاية
The reason why Yinling Valley had such a bad reputation,
إن سمعة وادي ين لينج سيئة للغاية
besides not facing the enemy head on
بالإضافة إلى عدم مواجهة الأعداء مباشرة
which is sneaky,
‫يبدو أنه متستر‬
was that the competition mechanism was cruel and ruthless.
هذا النوع من المنافسة قاسية وقسوة
Being able to sit firmly in the position of Young Master
إذا يمكنك أن تجلس في منصب ابن الوادي
also shows that you are a talent.
موهوب
It might not be the case
في المستقبل
in the future.
لا أعرف
Run!
اركض